Today, Irwan and I are going
to be giving a talk on scaling
transformers through sparsity.
And the kind of sparsity we're
going to be talking about today
is the kind where each input
can get either a different set
of weights or have a different
amount of computation applied
to it.
Irwan, do you want
to start it off?
Yep.
So I guess, the
overall motivation
for this line of work is
that the community has
kind of realized
that scale is perhaps
one of the most important
axes to focus on for obtaining
strong performance.
And there's almost this
sort of ongoing arms race
right now with different labs
and different institutions
sort of competing for
training the largest models.
And so maybe this dates back
from early 2020 with a paper
from OpenAI called "Scaling Laws
for Neural Language Models,"
where they find that
model performance follows
a predictable power law,
scales sort of as a power
law with model size in terms
of either compute, also
just parameters.
And so this scaling
law kind of generalizes
over multiple
orders of magnitude.
And that gives us the
confidence that if we
are to train very
large models, we
can expect performance just
by extrapolating these scaling
laws.
So in that paper, they also
find the interesting observation
that, basically, larger models
are more sample-efficient.
And so if you have a
fixed compute budget,
you can predict what
is the size, what
is the optimal model size,
for a fixed compute budget.
And the overall
observation is that you'd
rather train very large
models for less tests
than train smaller models
on more training steps.
And so these models
are scaled through--
basically, the paper
focuses on dense models,
right, where you just
increase the model dimensions.
But they're not
looking at sparsity.
And so sparsity
is a new dimension
that you can use to
scale architectures.
And this is sort of
the focus of the talk.
And so the sparsity we are
mentioning here is basically,
you will have sparsely
activated weights
based on the network inputs.
So every input will go to
a roughly similar amount
of computation but will be
applied different weights.
And so this dates back
to 1991 with a paper
called "Adaptive Mixtures
of Local Experts"
and was recently revisited by
Noam Shazeer and colleagues
at Google Brain with
LSTMs, where they replaced
some of the feedforward
networks and LSTMs
with mixture of experts.
And so the way this
works, or roughly,
is that you will have multiple
experts, each implementing
a small network or,
in that case, I think,
just a dense matrix
multiplication.
And so you have an additional
gating network, shown in green
here, that outputs a probability
distribution of our experts
that each token
should be sent to.
So this probability distribution
is computed as a softmax.
And once you have it,
you select a few experts.
So there are
different strategies.
Maybe we'll talk
about it later on.
And the output is simply
sort of the weighted mixture
of all selected
experts' outputs.
So they've been
pretty successful,
primarily in translation.
But there were some complexities
that have a broader use in NLP.
And so the switch transformer
paper addresses some of those.
And we'll be discussing how
to fix training instabilities
or reduce communication costs
and reduce model complexity.
All right, Barret,
do you want to go?
Sure, yeah.
So one kind of
approach that we're
going to have for sparsity
is the switch transformer,
which is kind of like a
simplified mixture of expert
variants, along with some other
improved training and fine
tuning techniques that allow
it to be stably trained
and also perform
better when fine tuned
on a lot of downstream tasks.
And so the switch
transformer kind of model
works with the following.
So you have some
transformer model
that has self-attention
and feedforward layers.
And the idea is that we replace
maybe one every two or one
every four feedforward layers
with a switch transformer
layer.
So you can see on the left is
one kind of layer block, which
is self-attention,
and add normalize,
then a feedforward layer,
then add normalize.
And in this case,
we're replacing
the normal feedforward
layer with the switch layer.
And we can see an illustration
of this on the right.
So on the right, we can see
that the layer has two inputs.
One is the token more.
The other is the
token parameters.
And we can see that these
embedding representations will
get sent to a router, which
is exactly how it works
in the mixture of experts.
So the router is
basically just going
to be getting a distribution
over all of the experts.
So in this case, we can see
that the highest probability
is going to expert number
two out of the four experts.
And then the right
token is actually
having the most probability on
the first feedforward weight,
which is like the first expert.
So yeah, we can see here
that what we're going to do
is in the switch transformer,
which is very simple.
It's just send it to the
highest probability expert.
And so here, we can see where
the adaptive computation lies,
where we'll have
four sets of weights.
There's some shared
weights and computation
across all the tokens.
For example, the
self-attention layer
is computed exactly the
same for the more token
and for the parameters token.
But in the sparse
switch layer, we
can see that,
actually, the inputs,
while having the same amount
of floating-point operations
applied to them, actually have
different weight matrices.
Next slide.
Yeah, so that's the
kind of high-level idea
with switch transformer
is that instead
of sending a token to multiple
different experts, which
can also increase the
communication costs,
as I'll go into a
little bit later,
it also just significantly
kind of simplifies
the algorithm by just only
sending it to one expert.
So for the improved
training methodology,
we focused on three
different things
to help improve the
training of sparse models.
The first was
selected precision,
which allows these
sparse models to be
trained in lower-precision
formats, which
is incredibly important.
Most of the models
we train, we really
don't want to be using
float32 because it's
just slower to compute.
And also, when you're
communicating tensors
across different
processors and stuff,
it's twice as slow just because
there's twice as many things.
Also, we have some
initialization tricks
and some training
tricks, as well,
for allowing them to
be trained more stably,
especially as the
models grow in size,
which is like a new
initialization method,
along with like a change to
the learning rate schedule.
And third, since our models
have so many more parameters,
we do notice definitely
different overfitting dynamics,
especially once we fine
tune these models that
have been pretrained
on all of the internet,
on these small tasks,
with maybe only 50,000
to 100,000 examples, that
they can be much more
prone to overfitting.
So we also look at some
custom regularization
to help prevent some of the
overfitting that we observe.
And finally, we also talk
about this differentiable load
balancing technique
we make, which kind of
allows each expert to roughly
get the same amount of tokens.
Because this is very
important, especially
given that we want the stuff
to be efficient on hardware.
We want, roughly, each expert to
have similar amounts of tokens
sent to it.
And so to kind of
encourage this,
we tack on an additional
load-balancing loss,
along with our cross-entropy
loss that we're training with.
Next slide.
OK, so here, I'm going to
go into selective precision.
So, yeah, again, so when
we're training large models,
it's really important that we
should be able to train them
in lower-precision formats.
So instead of each weight
and activation being 32 bits,
we want to shrink
it down to 16 bits.
And we use the bfloat16
representation.
And what we found
out of the gate
is that these models
are just unstable,
especially the sparse
models are much more
unstable than the dense
models in terms of you'll
train it for 10,000,
20,000 steps,
and then the losses
would just diverge.
This was something that
we frequently encountered.
And so one key
thing that we found
is that, basically,
you need to be casting
a part of the computation
in float32 for these models
to be able to be trained stably.
And the key component that we
found that you need to cast
is the router computation.
And essentially-- we can go
into the technical details
a little bit more
later-- but basically,
any time that there's these
exponentiation functions,
it's very important
that we are having
higher and higher precision
because of round-off errors
that can then drastically
change the output of some kind
of exponentiation function.
So for example, if you have
an exponentiation function
and you change it by
0.1 or 0.2 or 0.3,
this can drastically change the
output of exponentiating it,
especially depending on
how large the input is.
So yeah, this was a
very important thing.
And it basically doesn't
change the compute at all
and allows the models to just
be significantly more stable.
Next slide.
So the second thing
we looked at is also
the initialization scale.
So the standard way that we
were initializing these models,
we found to also just
make the models much more
prone to being unstable
and/or just performing worse.
So one thing that we did that
we found was very effective
was to just simply
make the initialization
scale much smaller.
And when we did this, we
found that the quality just
drastically improved.
And it was a very simple fix.
Next slide.
And the third thing
I mentioned, where,
since we noticed that
these models are much more
prone to overfitting, since
they just have significantly
more parameters, is that we
also use much more dropout
for the expert layers only.
So here, we can see we
have the T5 base, which
is a dense model.
And then we have a bunch of
different switch variants
on that.
And we've found to be the
most effective on these four
different fine
tuning tasks was just
to really significantly
increase the dropout
rate inside the expert layers.
And we found that this was
pretty effective for combating
the overfitting.
Barret?
Yeah?
We have a question from
one of the students.
Oh, awesome.
OK.
OK, let me take a look.
Do you want to go ahead?
I can ask.
It was just, in reference
to that previous table where
you have throughput
and precision,
it just seemed
surprising to me that you
could match this 1390
number while using
selective precision.
It seems like I would expect
it to be something in between.
Yeah.
So essentially, it
comes down to the fact
that there's maybe a
little bit of noise
sampled with the speed.
And the only part we're casting
is the router, which is maybe
such a insignificant
portion of the computation,
and there's zero
communication there,
that it's essentially like a
free operation in the network.
So whether you cast it
to bfloat16 or float32,
it doesn't actually
impact the speed at all,
within the precision that we
can actually measure the speed.
And also, these architectures
only use fast layer around one
every four layers.
And so, essentially,
the float32 policy
is kind of very negligible
in the entire architecture.
Yeah, it's like, for example, I
think, off the top of my head,
it's like 1/40 the
computation that it would cost
for you to do the first weight
matrix multiply in a ReLU
dense layer or something.
So it's a very, very small part.
And yeah, we're not using
them very frequently,
like Irwan mentioned, as well.
Got it.
OK, thanks.
Yeah.
And then, just a
quick point on this--
I won't go into some of the
technical details-- but yeah,
we definitely, since we're
training these things
on hardware and we really--
I think a big part of the
mixture of experts paradigm
is that these things are
designed such that it maps
really efficiently to hardware.
So we want to be doing
dense matrix multiplies.
And for this to
work really well,
we also want to be able to have
roughly equal amount of tokens
going to each of the
different experts.
And I think this isn't that
sensitive to the load-balancing
formulation.
We tried a few things.
A lot of them worked.
But essentially,
you definitely want
some kind of load-balancing loss
added on when using sparsity.
Yeah, next slide.
Oh, that's me.
Yeah, Irwan, go ahead.
Yeah, so the frameworks
with the library
we use rely on
static shapes for--
so XLA, so the compiler for
TensorFlow and Mesh TensorFlow
expect static
shapes for tensors.
However, the computations
in switch transformers
are dynamic because
of the router, right?
Different inputs will be
routed to different experts.
And so we need to specify ahead
of time how many tokens will
be sent to each expert.
And so we will introduce this
expert capacity hyperparameter
to specify that.
And it's going to be
a static number which
says how many tokens
each expert can process.
And so in practice, we
instead parameterize this
by having a quantity
called the capacity factor.
So we have an example here.
So the bottom row is a bunch
of tokens on one device.
And then you need
to sort of route
those tokens to multiple
devices, or multiple experts.
So if too many tokens are
routed to a single expert,
some tokens will be dropped
because, as we said,
an expert has a fixed capacity.
So that's the
example on the left,
where the capacity factor is 1.
And that basically means
that the toll does not
like extra buffer
for routing tokens.
So instead of that, we
can use a capacity factor
that's larger than 1.
So on the right, you
have an example with 1.5.
So that means that now, each
expert has sort of three slots.
They can process three tokens.
And so that prevents
token dropping
because we have more capacity.
But the issue is that
this means higher--
this means more expensive
communication across devices.
Yeah.
OK, so-- yeah, go ahead.
So one thing that we
also experimented with
was this method called
no token left behind.
And the idea was the following.
So since we have to have a
fixed batch size for each expert
and there can be token
dropping, we kind of
were thinking that, hey,
yeah, having tokens drop,
or having some tokens not
having any computation
applied to it is probably
hurting the model performance.
So what if we do a
multi-stage routing procedure?
So first, you do
the normal routing,
where it's like you send
each token to its highest
probability expert.
But then any dropped
tokens, you then
send to their second-highest
probability expert
and so forth and so on,
where you can basically
repeat this process to
guarantee that no tokens are
being dropped.
Interestingly,
actually, this approach
didn't empirically
improve model performance.
If anything, it actually
kind of hurt it.
And we thought that was
actually very interesting.
And I think the intuition is
that once the model learns
it wants to send a
token to one expert,
it really wants to have that
computation applied to it.
And just applying
some other computation
doesn't have, at all,
the same property,
along with it, actually, maybe
being potentially detrimental.
So yeah, we thought that
was pretty interesting,
as we were very optimistic
this would potentially
get improved performance.
But it ended up not really
making a difference.
And we found this
quite surprising.
We have a question from--
I think it will
actually kind of address
the majority of the last
point that you brought up.
I think when I think about a
mixture of experts, usually,
they specialize in
different things, right?
So I think this just a lot--
I was just wondering if you
send it to the second best
or whatever, what if
all of your tokens
would be particularly
good for one expert,
and then you only process,
let's say, 20% of your tokens.
So that ends up being
better than rerouting them
to anything else.
Exactly.
Yeah, so even if you're
dropping a lot of tokens,
it's not beneficial to be
sending them to the second,
third, or fourth best thing.
And one, actually,
interesting property
that we noticed about
these models is they're
surprisingly robust
to token dropping,
especially during fine tuning.
So yeah, in the standard
paradigm, what we'll do
is we'll pretrain this thing.
We'll have some
load-balancing loss,
which makes the tokens
pretty balanced, actually.
But then, during
fine tuning, where
it's like we really want to
fine tune it on a specific task,
we actually studied
this exact question.
And we were studying,
does it help
to have a load-balancing loss
during fine tuning or not?
And so if you have the
load-balancing loss,
yeah, that kind
of is encouraging.
For the specific
task, we want to try
to have all the experts be
used versus turning it off,
where there's definitely
some prior specialization.
And it's actually
much better to just
turn the auxiliary loss off.
And even if it's 60% to 70% of
the tokens are being dropped,
that actually
performs much better
than having all
the tokens balance.
But doesn't a
load-balancing loss
encourage, basically,
all the experts
to learn very similar weights
and then just randomly
assign your tokens?
Because then it
doesn't matter to which
expert stuff is being sent to.
So when we use the
load-balancing loss,
the routing mechanism
is definitely learned.
So the model definitely
is encouraged
to choose an expert
that it wants to send it
to for good [INAUDIBLE].
Right.
But if all the experts
learn the same weights,
then the router learns,
basically, oh, it
doesn't matter
where I send it to.
So if you encourage
load balancing,
you encourage, technically,
that you want any loss
to fit with any expert, right?
That's maybe the
extreme behavior
if you have a very high
sort of load-balancing loss
coefficient.
But in practice, that
coefficient is kind of tuned,
and we observe that,
for small enough values,
the router still learns
semantic, meaningful routing.
Yeah.
Because it's like a balance
between this cross-entropy loss
and this load-balancing loss.
And so, on one hand,
yeah, you definitely
want to encourage the
model to be balanced.
Then, on the other
hand, you also
want it to just get good
empirical performance.
And yeah, the model is able
to definitely, on one hand,
learn and specialize
the experts where
they have different weights such
that it's like, definitely, it
expects certain tokens to
be sent to certain experts
but, on the other hand,
still be reasonably balanced
so that the models
are efficiently
run on modern hardware.
Exactly.
And we also have a question
from the classroom.
So the question I want to ask
is it seems to me like this
is a very experimental talk.
We're talking about
floating-point precision.
different approaches
that currently work well.
And whenever we're dealing
with empirical science,
there's a question of, what
is the research question?
And I feel like I missed that.
So what are we trying to answer
with all these experiments?
Yeah, I think the high-level
research question is, can we
create models that are
doing adaptive computation
from the standpoint
of, can we try
to make models more simulate the
dynamics that we think models
should most naturally use,
which is different inputs have
different amounts of
computation applied,
have different weights
applied to them,
and basically all of this?
Basically, we're trying to
research and figure out,
how can we create a new
framework for these models
to be trained, as opposed to
their dense counterparts that,
for every input,
are always having
the same exact
computation applied?
So that's interesting.
Because when you say the same
exact computation applied,
one might imagine that--
to me, the immediate
thing is about how long
to deliberate about something.
What I mean by that is if we
want to have variable length
computation, you
could imagine that I
could have a short
amount of computation,
or I could have much
longer computation.
But this idea of why,
then, do we instead
consider the dimension of
different computation--
assuming, of course, that
these experts do indeed
learn different
things, which I think
you'll get to in a minute.
So why do we immediately
jump to thinking
about specialized
experts, as opposed
to thinking about variable
length computation?
So yeah, so this
is actually-- we
actually go into some variable
length computation stuff
later in the talk.
And I feel like they're both,
actually, just important axes
that should both be pushed on.
Yeah, I guess it's kind of--
I guess what I'm
trying to understand--
I'm not phrasing
my question well.
What I'm trying to understand is
your thinking about why did you
decide to attack this one first?
I want to understand
why your team chose
to go this direction first.
Yeah, absolutely.
So I think that,
one, empirically, it
seems that sparsity has led
to better empirical results
in the field of deep learning
than adaptive computation
so far.
And I think the way that we
use these things maps really
well to our modern hardware,
which is also very promising.
And I think the way we
were kind of looking at it
is sparsity is a first
step towards doing
more interesting and general
adaptive computation.
Because I think it's like
this stuff is complicated.
And typically, starting from
something that works well
is better than necessarily
trying something
that's not necessarily
as proven out
and then trying to get
it to work really well.
So I think we're kind of
starting from sparsity, which
Noam Shazeer and others
got to work really
well in the context of LSTMs.
We were kind of
interested in, let's port
some of this to transformers.
Let's get it
working really well.
And then, let's
slowly start expanding
towards a lot of the
other natural questions
that you mentioned,
where it's like, OK,
whereas instead of
different weights per core,
let's also maybe have a
different computation per core
and all of this.
So that's, I guess,
how we were kind
of building the natural
build-up and progression
of our research.
Got it.
Cool.
Thank you.
Yeah.
What do you think, Irwan?
Anything else to add?
Yeah, I guess I kind of
see adaptive computation
and sparsity as related
but separate things.
So sparsity is more like
different parameters
for each example.
And adaptive
computation might be
more different amount of flux.
And we have some of that
with the token dropping,
but that's not the
main domain motivation.
Definitely, as
Barret mentioned, I
would say no one
really has figured out
adaptive computation
yet for deep learning.
And one reason is because
we have these accelerators
where I expect, sort of--
we need to work with a batch,
like data parallelism, right?
And all of our accelerators
and our frameworks
use this SPMD
paradigm where we're
kind of supposed to apply the
same computation to examples.
And so if you look
at the literature,
you have works like
universal transformers
where they replaced the
feedforwards in the transformer
by just a recurrent weight.
And so it's kind of like
an LSTM on each token.
And the LSTM can stop
at different times
based on some criteria.
But the way these
things are implemented
is just through masking.
Because it needs
to be implemented
in the SPMD programming style.
And so definitely,
sparsity was kind of easier
to get to work first.
And also, there were some prior
results with LSTMs, so yeah.
In terms of the first
question, what's
the research question
here, it's just like, oh,
can we design more
efficient models?
And sparsity is
this new axis that
hasn't been explored that much.
And, yeah, I think that
I'm happy with just setting
the research question, yeah.
Great.
OK.
Yeah, so next slide.
Yeah, again, so kind of
putting it all together.
So the switch transformer
layer selects an expert, just
the top expert, and
then incorporates
a bunch of the general
sparse model improvements
to allow it to fine
tune better, allow
it to be more
regularized, allow it
to be trained with
lower-precision formats
and a lot of technical
details to just get
them training and working well.
So yeah, one thing that
we also wanted to do
was a comparison between
top-1 and top-2 routing,
since top-2 routing was
the most popular technique.
And so here, we can see we have
two different dense models,
trained on different sizes.
And we're going to be looking
at the pretraining negative log
perplexity.
So yeah, the bigger
the number, the better.
So next slide.
And what we're
going to be doing is
we're going to be studying them
at different capacity factors.
So a capacity factor
of 2.0 basically
means that there is enough
buffer for two tokens
to be sent to every
single expert.
And we're going to be comparing
top one versus top two
routing and also
comparing their speeds,
along with their time to
get some threshold quality.
OK, so here, we can see in
the capacity factor 2.0 case
that the MoE models outperform
switch transformer, which
makes a lot of sense.
Since switch transformer is
only sending a top-1 token
to each expert, the mixture of
expert is sending two tokens.
So that makes sense
that this extra buffer
will be disproportionately
beneficial for the mixture
of expert models.
And so we noticed that.
And next slide, or, yeah, next.
Now so the really interesting
parts for the top-1 routing
becomes when we lower
the capacity factors.
So having a high
capacity factor is
bad for many
reasons, one of which
is it really incurs more of
these communication costs
for sending tokens to
the correct experts.
It also incurs
more compute costs
and also incurs a lot
of memory overhead.
So if you can get
this lower, it's
usually a very, very good thing.
And so what we see here is that
switch transformer actually
outperforms mixture of experts
when you have a lower capacity
factor.
And we can see that the
time to quality threshold,
we get there much quicker.
And so even across the 2.0
and the 1.25 capacity factors,
the kind of Pareto optimal
thing we saw in our setup
is to use switch transformer
at a lower capacity factor,
just due to the fact that
while the quality is worse,
a little bit worse,
on a step basis,
it's just much faster to run.
So it's kind of the
Pareto optimal decision.
Next slide.
And we could also be seeing
that, for capacity factor 1.0,
again, we can see that this
really disproportionately
benefits switch transformer
and is even better on a Pareto
standpoint than the
1.25 capacity factors.
And interestingly,
since MoE also
does a little bit
more computation,
you can also just increase
the amount of compute
done elsewhere in the model.
And we can see that that's a
much more efficient allocation
of compute.
So yeah, overall,
our takeaway is
that lower capacity
factors using top-1 routing
is more Pareto-efficient than
using top-2 routing at higher
capacity factors.
Next slide.
Irwan, you can take it over.
OK.
So next, we'll look at how
switch transformer scales
as a function of the number of
experts in the switch layers.
And so on the right
side here, you
see a plot that shows
perplexity versus
training steps for different
switch architectures,
ranging from T5 base,
which is basically
no expert or a single
expert, up to 128 experts.
And so you see that, as we
increase the number of experts,
which also increases the
number of parameters,
sparse parameters, you
get sort of speed-ups.
You get increasing speed-ups
above the dense baseline
and also sort of diminishing
returns to multiplying,
to increasing, the number
of experts, as well.
So the previous figure
was looking at perplexity
versus training steps.
Here, we look at perplexity
versus training time.
So that includes all the
additional communication costs
when you have more
experts, comparing
to the dense baseline.
And so this is for
switch-based or dense T5 base.
And we observe up to 7X
speedups of our T5 base.
And so just to,
maybe, contextualize
these numbers, 7X
speedups in deep learning
are pretty hard to obtain.
And so I think this is
one of the results that
can spark a lot of
interest in sparse models,
even if it's only for
pretraining for now,
just having that number is
maybe there's a significant--
there's something significant
that can be happening here.
OK, so sparse scaling laws.
So here, we'll look at sort
of loss versus sparse model
parameters, which are
increased by increasing
the number of experts.
And so similarly to the
neural scaling lab paper,
we observed that as you
increase the parameters,
the sparse parameters,
and keep the FLOPS fixed,
you get consistent gains
but diminishing gains.
OK, so now, we're going to
compare expert parallelism
and model parallelism.
So we introduced sparsity,
or expert parallelism,
as a new dimension
to scale models.
But of course,
there's the other one
for dense model, which is
simply model parallelism, where
model weights are partitioned
across cores once they
are above the maximum size that
you can feed on a single core.
All right, so to the left
is expert parallelism here.
Yeah.
So essentially, what
we're doing is yeah,
we're kind of comparing
a switch-based model
versus the dense-based.
And we're also comparing
against the larger dense model
that has used model parallelism.
And we can see that--
because basically, when we
want to scale up model size,
we kind of have two axes that
we can either go through.
We can either increase
the number of FLOPS
by scaling through
model parallelism
or increase the number
of parameters by scaling
through sparsity.
And so we can see that, even
compared to a dense model
that's been scaled up
through model parallelism,
that sparsity is
still, at this scale,
a more effective way to scale up
the model by still getting 2.5X
speedups over this larger dense
model that was using model
parallelism.
Cool.
So next slide.
Yeah.
Basically, here, T5-large
is the dense model
that uses model parallelism.
Barret, go ahead.
OK.
And so one thing that we
also wanted to look at
is are these expert
models effective
if you have a really
small amount of compute
or just a small
amount of experts?
So typically, when we're
designing these models,
we have one expert per core.
But if you don't have a large
cluster to run these things
on-- let's say you just
have a GPU with two cores
or something--
I guess is having two
experts more effective
than just a dense model?
And the answer is yes.
So we can see even pretty
good scaling properties,
even with a tiny
amount of experts,
which is very promising for
these models to be used,
even in much lower
compute regimes.
Next slide.
Irwan, you want to go ahead?
OK, yeah.
So we'll look at
what things look
like when we use different types
of parallelism, namely expert
parallelism, to add experts,
model parallelism to shared
model ways across cores and,
also, their parallelism, which
is sort of the dominant paradigm
in deep learning at the moment.
And so I guess, in
the previous slides,
we mostly talked about
expert parallelism.
But of course, dense models
and large-scale dense models
use model parallelism.
So GPT-3 and other large
models, what they do
is that they will simply
shove models weights
across different cores.
We have a question.
Oh.
Yeah, I just wanted to know
because I think there was--
I don't know if you're
going to address later--
but I think
somewhere in a paper,
it said that the more
experts you have,
the more
sample-efficient it gets.
And I was just hoping
that you could give us
some intuition about that.
Because I don't understand
why that would be the case.
So I guess-- yeah, maybe
Irwan should take this.
So I guess there's all of
this work on larger models are
more sample-efficient.
And larger in the context
of the scaling law works
means more parameters
and more FLOPS.
As you increase the
number of experts,
there's more parameters
but not more FLOPS.
But the model is still
larger in a similar sense.
So I guess, building
on the intuition
that larger models are more
sample-efficient, in my mind,
it's not necessarily
that surprising
that these models
with more experts that
have more parameters are
more sample-efficient.
I guess that's my kind of
high-level intuition for it.
Yeah, I would say
that's kind of expected
that more experts leads to
better sample efficiency,
especially if you look at the
training step and the training
time.
OK, cool.
So where were we?
OK, so we'll look at how models
weights are split over cores
for different scenarios.
So data parallelism
is the first one.
So that's kind of
the typical setup
that deep learning
uses, especially
for not-so-large
networks which don't
require model parallelism.
And so let me explain how--
yeah, I'll just go to the
final figure right now
and explain how to
look at this figure.
OK, so we have 16 processes,
which are organized in the 4
by 4 mesh, right?
So each dotted line, each
4 by 4 dotted line here,
represents a different core.
And the first row studies
how the model weights
are split over cores.
And the second row
illustrates how data--
so literally, examples and
tokens-- are split over cores.
And then the final
thing that's required
to understand this
figure is that each color
of the shaded squares here
identifies a unique weight
matrix
So let's start with
data parallelism.
So for data parallelism,
the same model weights
are replicated across all cores.
And the data is simply
partitioned over cores.
And so that's what this
corresponds to, if you like,
using the description of
the caption, the explanation
of the caption, I just gave.
So next, we have
model parallelism.
That's kind of just like
a theoretical example.
Because in practice,
people always
use model parallelism
in conjunction
with data parallelism.
But if you were to do
only model parallelism,
then you would have a
single model weight that
is partitioned over all cores.
And your data would just be
replicated over all cores,
instead.
So now we have model
and data parallelism.
And that's kind of
the typical scenario
for large dense networks.
So in that case, model
weights are partitioned
among a subset of the cores,
the subset of cores that process
different batches of data.
And so in that example
here, we have sort of four--
so the first
sub-square here means
that the model weights are
partitioned across four cores.
And this is replicated four
times for the data parallelism
dimension.
On the data side for modeling
and data parallelism,
the data here is replicated
across model parallel cores
and partitioned across
data parallel cores.
So next, we have expert
and data parallelism.
So in that scenario, that's kind
of similar to data parallelism.
But now, each core will
hold a different model
weight, which is illustrated
by the different colors.
And for the data side, the
data is simply replicated--
sorry, there is partition
across all cores,
just like in the data
parallelism scenario.
And so finally, we have the
rightmost column, which is--
I guess that's the setup used
in the switch transformer
paper for the larger models.
And so here, for the
model partitioning,
each expert is partitioned
across multiple cores.
So in that example,
we have four experts,
each partitioned
across four cores.
And the data is replicated
across multiple parallel cores
and partitioned across
data parallel cores.
So that's all a bit complex
to understand orally.
But the switch transformer
paper has the same figure
with a nice caption
to explain it.
And yeah, maybe
we can, Barret, we
can add something
quickly about how this
is implemented in practice.
So there's this paper called
Mesh Transformer, which kind of
extends batch or
data parallelism
to more general purpose,
SPMD-style programming.
And so different labs
have different frameworks.
But this paper kind
of lays the foundation
for general
SPMD-distributed computing,
which is required for
training large-scale models.
And so under the
mesh abstraction,
basically, we have
a mesh of processes.
And so that mesh has
dimensions, named dimensions.
And these named
dimensions specify
how the tensor dimensions will
be partitioned, or replicated,
across the mesh dimensions.
And so just that
simple abstraction
supports sort of
data parallelism
or some other parallelism and
especially expert parallelism
at once.
And so I invite whoever is
interested to also check
that paper.
Because that kind of
lays the foundation
for understanding these things.
All right, Barret, want to go?
Cool.
Yeah, so next, we
are going to talk
about how we take these
parallelism strategies
and kind of combine them
together to make a 1.6 trillion
parameter sparse model.
So next slide.
So what we ended up
doing in this work
was we trained two different
very large sparse models.
And we compared them to
the largest T5 models.
So we can see the T5-XXL,
which is a dense model,
and it was the largest one
trained in the T5 paper.
And it has around 13
billion parameters.
And here, we list a lot
of the model dimensions,
like dmodel, dff, which are just
the various sizes and shapes
of the tensors and stuff,
the number of layers,
the number of heads.
And importantly, we also mention
the negative log perplexity
at step 250k and at 500k.
And yeah, so we designed
two sparse models
to test how scaling versus
sparsity versus scaling
versus sparsity and FLOPS work.
So first, let me talk
about Switch-XXL.
So that has the same amount
of FLOPS per token as T5-XXL
but has 64 experts.
And this leads it to have
around 400 billion parameters.
And we can see that
on a step basis,
it actually performs quite
well and outperforms the T5-XXL
by quite a good margin.
Interestingly, though, the
third model we designed,
Switch-C, which has
1.6 trillion parameters
but has significantly
fewer FLOPS, almost 10 less
flops per token than either
of the above two models.
So it's really trading
by reducing FLOPS
to have way more
sparse parameters.
And we can see on a step
basis the switch-C model works
well but not as
well as, actually,
the higher FLOP model.
But on a kind of a
Pareto axis, where
we are looking at TPU hours
on the x-axis and not step,
the Switch-C model
actually outperforms them
both by a pretty large margin.
So for pretraining
performance, we're
seeing that,
actually, just having
a lot of sparsity and less FLOPS
actually can be quite good.
Next slide.
So again, those
two sparse models
are really trying to
get at this hypothesis
that, actually,
Noam Shazeer had,
which is that parameters
are good for more
knowledge, reasoning.
And compute, aka FLOPS,
is good for intelligence.
And so we're going to try
to get at that by taking
these different sparse models
and then fine tuning them
on different tasks,
some of which
require more knowledge and
then others which require more
of reasoning, for whatever
like hand-wavy definition
we want to give that.
So yeah, so for a
fixed-- oh, go back.
So for a fixed--
could you go back to
the previous slide?
Oh, yeah.
Sorry.
OK, so for a fixed quality on
an upstream pre-training task,
yeah, do parameters
independently matter?
So we're going to look at
two tasks here, one of which
is SuperGLUE, which is
kind of our reasoning task.
And then another
is TriviaQA, which
is some knowledge
task, where it's
like you just give
it a question,
and you have it
output an answer.
OK, and so here,
we're going to take
a look at superGLUE quality.
So we can see on the x-axis is
the pretraining performance.
And the y-axis is the SuperGLUE
score after fine tuning.
And interestingly, we
can see, definitely,
that the sparse models
definitely are, for a fixed,
pretraining perplexity,
do worse on fine tuning.
This can be especially
noticed at the upper right
portion of the plot, where the
dense models are definitely
fine tuning better than
their sparse counterpart.
Next slide.
Interestingly, when we
study it on the more
knowledge-heavy tasks,
the sparse model
for a fixed
pretraining perplexity
does disproportionately well.
So for a model that roughly
has the same perplexity,
we're getting
really large boosts
for these knowledge-heavy tasks.
So this is pretty interesting.
And it also really shows some
of the dangers of comparing only
on your pretraining metrics.
So these models could have the
same exact pretraining metric
but very different properties
when fine tuning them
on different tasks.
Next slide.
And interestingly, so yeah,
all of the switch models
here are just various
models that have,
still, a good amount of FLOPS.
But the red model is
actually the 1.6 trillion
parameter sparse model
that has very few FLOPS
but a lot, a lot of parameters.
And you can see that
as the red dot here.
And it does, actually,
disproportionately bad compared
to other sparse models that also
have pretty good perplexities.
And so yeah, it's
definitely very interesting.
And it shows that, for
models during pretraining
that have a lot of
sparsity, they definitely
suffer on some of these
more reasoning-heavy metrics
but do disproportionately
well for more
of these knowledge-heavy tasks.
Next slide.
And so here, we can see
it as just a huge outlier
for pretraining perplexity,
doing just incredibly well
on this downstream
question answering task.
Next slide, yeah.
OK, so also, one thing
that we were going to do
is just look at the fine tuning
properties of sparse models
across a few scales and
just see how they perform.
Next slide.
And yeah, so here, we
try two different models.
One is T5-base, and then we
make a FLOP-matched sparse
counterpoint.
And when they say
FLOP-matched, it's
like each token will have
the same amount of FLOPS,
but now we just have experts.
So we do this for
both base and large.
And we see that, actually,
across almost all tasks
besides two ARC tasks,
the sparse models
perform quite well, which
is definitely promising.
So we are seeing that these
models are pretty robust.
They pretrain well.
And then they also
fine tune well when
scaled appropriately by scaling
up both the FLOPS and sparsity,
whereas the negative
results we've really seen
are like when you just have a
huge amount of sparsity and not
too many FLOPS.
Next slide.
And one, also, thing
we wanted to look at
was the multilingual training.
So we were previously studying
all of this on English only.
And we also wanted to
see how sparsity helps
in the multilingual setting.
Because we also felt like this
would be a very natural place
for sparsity to work well,
where, potentially, experts
could specialize
across languages.
And we do see strong results.
So on 91% of the languages, I
think, of around 100 languages,
we see over at
least a 4X speed-up
over the mT5 dense model.
Next slide.
Irwan, you want to go ahead?
No.
Go.
Go ahead.
OK.
So yeah, another thing we wanted
to talk about was distillation.
So one downside of
these sparse models
is that they'll have a
lot more parameters, which
means that if you're serving
these things or something,
you either need high
throughput use cases
or you need to maybe distill
it back down into a smaller
dense model.
So here, what we do is we
look at like the T5-Base
and Switch-Base And we look at
its pretraining performance.
And then we go
through some ablations
of different
distillation techniques
and find that with
the best techniques,
we can keep around
30% of the quality
improvements of sparsity
while distilling it back down
into its dense counterpart.
So next slide.
Yeah, and then we
kind of studied
this across multiple scales.
And again, we see around
30% to 40% of the gains
can be kept when going
from a sparse model
and distilling it back down into
its FLOP-matched dense model.
So you can get rid of up
to 99% of the parameters
and still keep around 30%
of the improvements, which
is very promising.
Next slide.
Wait, I'm sorry.
Yeah?
All right.
Sorry about that.
Can you just say that
last sentence again?
You said that you can keep the
30% of the teacher's benefit.
Yeah, basically.
So exactly.
Yeah.
Sure.
Go on.
Yeah, so we're looking at,
yeah, you train a sparse model,
and then you
distill it back down
to a dense model versus training
a dense model from scratch.
And you look at the gap between
the sparse and dense model
from scratch versus the gap
between the dense and then
the distilled dense model.
What do you mean
by distilled model?
Yeah, go for it.
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
Yeah, maybe let me just do
a quick, high-level summary
again.
So what we'll do for
our comparisons is
we'll train a dense
model from scratch,
we'll train a sparse
and then we'll also
run a third experiment
where we distill that sparse
model down into a dense model.
What does distilling mean?
We're basically trying to match
the teacher's logits, the kind
of standard thing of
matching either the logits
or the soft probabilities
for each token
or something like that.
OK, if I can jump
in with my question.
So what I'm struggling
with is, how
do I interpret the
line that says percent
of teacher and performance?
Yeah, OK.
So it's basically
looking at the gap
between the dense
and sparse model.
So we'll have the dense
model get some performance.
We'll have the sparse
And then the dense model
distilled from the sparse model
would be somewhere in
between that range.
And we're basically saying
it's 30% through that range.
So in a 0 to 1
interval, it's like 0.3
of the way from the dense
to the sparse model.
I see.
So this is not saying that the
percent of teacher performance
does not mean that if
the teachers say it--
if we use the teacher's guesses
or predictions as the ground
truth, this is not saying that
the distilled model matches
with the teacher
33% of the time?
No, no, exactly.
It's basically saying you
get 30% of the quality
improvements.
Yeah, exactly.
OK, cool.
And then, if we can
back up this slide,
I had a different question,
but I didn't want to interrupt.
When we were talking about all
of these different T5 bases--
and then, also, a few
slides before this--
I don't know that much about T5.
I'm curious to know
when T5 is trained,
is there a weight penalty
in the loss function?
Is there a weight decay term?
No, there's no
weight decay training
with any of the sparse
or dense models.
I see.
So out of curiosity,
then, how do dense models
perform compared
to the switch model
if you add some sort of
weight regularization
that incentivizes getting
rid of useless weights?
Oh, so some kind of maybe L1
term or something like that.
Exactly, yeah.
So I'm just wondering how
much of-- because here,
we're talking about the
benefits of sparsity.
And I'm wondering how much
of this benefit from sparsity
is due to the fact that
just some of this--
I mean, effectively what
the switch model is doing,
if I understand correctly--
maybe I don't-- what I
understand is that the switch
model in the feedforward layer,
it's just like you fix
some the weight to be zero.
That's what it
means to be sparse.
Well, actually,
we're kind of really
trying to inject more weights.
So we're actually
kind of trying to do--
it's a little bit,
maybe, paradoxical.
Because we're saying
switch transformer,
but our idea is to be
like, hey, we actually
want to just have significantly
more weights, not less weights.
It's kind of like you
would zero out weights
but within a much larger weight
matrix, if that makes sense.
I see, yes.
And so to me, it seems like a
relevant baseline to just ask,
what happens if I
have the dense matrix
but I incentivize it
with, say, an L1 or L2
penalty on the weights?
And I'd be curious to
know how that compares.
Yeah, we didn't run this.
But also, that kind of gets rid
of weights for the dense model.
So if anything--
Sure, sure.
[INAUDIBLE]
So yeah, that --
Also-- and the last point is
if you just add an L1 penalty
loss, you're not going to
have structural sparsity,
where it's like, here,
it's not random weights
in your giant weight matrix
that are zeroed out, right?
It's really blocks depending--
or blocks corresponding
to each x part.
And so that structure allows
the whole communication stuff.
And that's just the
fact that you have
multiple cores [INAUDIBLE].
I totally agree with
that block structure.
And that's what
I'm trying to say
is that the switch
has this very rich--
it's not just sparse, it
also has this rich structure.
And what I'm trying to do
in my mind is disentangle,
is the sparsity what's
offering an advantage?
Or is this additional
structure that you've
built in, is that what
gives the performance gain?
So that's why I'm asking.
So the block structure
is what enables
to leverage the fact that
you have multiple cores.
If you didn't have
that block structure,
you'd still have to
route to everything.
And so you have more
communication costs and so on.
And then your first
question was what, sorry?
I'm not actually sure
if there was a question.
I guess what I'm trying to say
is I'm trying to disambiguate--
yeah, anyways.
But I agree.
It's a little bit weird.
Because sparsity kind
of is like a spectrum
of meaning false sparsity,
just, for example, compression.
And like model pruning
is a form of sparsity
but also through
transformer and MoE also
refer to it as sparsity.
And they're kind of related,
but definitely, they're
aiming at different things.
This is a really interesting
idea of it's sparse,
but you have more parameters.
I'll have to think
about that more.
Thank you.
Yeah, it's kind of sparse
within this giant weight
matrix, which is [INAUDIBLE].
Exactly, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I hadn't appreciated that.
So I appreciate you
pointing that out.
Thank you.
I have a follow-up question
on the distillation part.
Yeah, of course.
OK, so if you distill it
back down, now you have one--
technically, you're back to
the dense layer architecture,
right?
Mm-hmm.
So now, the entire
idea of expert
is that certain tokens would
be sent to different experts
because they just
like, I don't know,
are more specialized in figuring
something out about this token.
So now if you go back
to this dense layer,
aren't you basically
only serving
whichever expert you
based this dense layer on?
These tokens will
probably perform well,
and all the other tokens are
kind of left behind, right?
I'm actually-- sorry,
I don't think I'm fully
understanding your question.
So are you getting
at, we're distilling
this on a specific
data set so that--
I'm thinking about how
to use that, like what--
Yeah, so maybe concretely,
so for superGLUE,
let's say you want a server
model that does superGLUE well.
I think the idea
is that you distill
the sparse model into a
dense model on superGLUE.
So then you kind of get
this compressed dense model
that now performs
better than if you
were to just train
it from scratch
or train it from a
pretrained dense model.
So then it's like--
[INAUDIBLE] --to use, though.
Say that again?
You have to pick
one expert, right?
No, no, no.
You can just
distill all of the--
because they're just
matching the model outputs.
So you can just treat
the sparse model
as kind of a black box thing.
All we're doing is
just trying to have
the dense model match the
actual final token predictions.
Oh, god.
OK, got it.
OK.
Sorry.
I was not familiar with
the idea of distillation.
So I think that was
my entire confusion.
OK, thanks.
Yeah, of course.
Because I guess
one motivation here
is that having experts
can make solving
a little bit more
difficult. Because it
requires bigger topologies.
Let's say you have
eight experts.
You need-- well, I guess you can
have multiple experts on fewer
cores.
But let's just say they're a
little bit harder to solve.
And so if we can get the
benefits from sparsity
at pretraining, then use
distillation to a dense model
for solving, that
can be beneficial.
So I think that would solve the
motivation for that experiment,
right, Barret?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, exactly.
OK, where were we?
Yes, kind of just wrapping up.
Yeah, go ahead.
No, go ahead.
But I just had, I think,
one more student question.
So yeah.
Oh, yeah, go ahead.
[INAUDIBLE], ask it now.
Oh, yeah, yeah, sounds good.
Yeah, thanks, guys,
for the talk so far.
Just a quick question.
Was wondering if you think there
are any interesting directions
around building models that
are explicitly optimized
for parallel training?
I guess the MoE model seems like
it does a really good job here.
And also, at
inference time, it's
very useful to have fewer
FLOPS per computation
or for forward tasks.
But, I guess, do
you think that there
are any interesting
directions around distributed
training where you might have
models that are explicitly
architected to have a
lot of parallel heads
or other features that
are kind of embarrassingly
parallelizable?
Or does just using standard
scale up the models
by adding more layers
and then just get away
with using model and data
parallelism work well enough?
Yeah.
So I think-- so let me just make
sure I'm fully understanding.
So I think also, right now,
even our models are definitely
very co-designed with the
hardware and the shapes
and things.
So yeah, I think
at a high level,
yes, I think there's a ton
of interesting research
on co-designing the hardware,
the partitioning algorithms,
and the models.
I think, given that
we have this kind
of SPMD mesh-style
partitioning, we
are already designing our models
in ways that fit it really
well.
So for example, when we
want to scale up our model,
one of the first dimensions
we go to scale up
is the internal
hidden dimension.
Because there's some
really nice properties
of scaling up this dimension.
It basically becomes kind
of independent to some
of the communication costs.
It's really good when
looking at the compute
to memory operations on these
compute devices and stuff.
[INAUDIBLE]
Yeah, exactly.
I think when we're even
designing these models,
we're really setting
dimensions such
that it maps well into hardware.
So it's almost like, given
that we have this model data
parallelism, we're actually
designing models more for it.
But I also think
that there's a ton
of new, interesting,
distributed algorithms and stuff
like that which makes designing
models very interesting.
I think one thing that
I think is really cool
is the Microsoft ZeRO
partitioning, too,
which also adds some really nice
implications for how to design
and scale models and stuff.
So yeah, I think this is a very
fruitful research direction,
if that kind of
answered your question.
Yeah, no, that was super
helpful and interesting.
Thanks.
Yeah, yeah, definitely.
I'm very optimistic
on the future
of us designing the
hardware, the model,
the partitioning
strategies all together.
Because really, to
get it to work well,
you kind of have to
know about all three
and kind of intertwine
the development of them.
Yeah, that sounds awesome.
Cool.
Yeah, so just to summarize,
so switch transformer
is a nice simplification
over mixture of experts.
And we're seeing that we
get really strong speedup
improvements on pretraining over
a lot of the T5 models, which
are very strong baselines.
We're seeing that
we can efficiently
distill the sparse
models back to dense ones
and get improved both
pretraining and fine tuning
through some of these newer
techniques we talked about.
And we're also seeing that
the models are working
on multilingual data and that
we can now easily successfully
train up to 1.6 trillion
parameter models, which
is pretty promising.
And next slide.
And so we also wanted to go
into two slides about some newer
work about actually using these
kind of models for computer
vision and, actually,
also a little bit
of how they can be
used to actually
do some level of
adaptive computation,
where not only now, each input
gets different weights but also
sometimes, different inputs
will have different amounts
of compute applied to it.
And so there is some really
great work of doing this out
of the Google Zurich team.
And yeah, they're just doing
it for image classification.
And they're basically
seeing a lot
of the similar types of
scaling properties, where
scaling up the number of
experts and using sparsity
allows them to get good
performance design, image
classification.
Next slide.
And interestingly, one
of the things they do
is, as we talked about
the capacity factor.
So we were talking about
values of 1, 1.25, 2.0,
which means at a
value of 2.0, there's
buffer for two
tokens per expert.
But they actually study
it going less than 1.
So that means that
at 0.5, that means
there's only room for
half the number of tokens.
And the nice part
is that they did
this for image classification.
And also, in images, there's
just a lot of redundancy.
And they notice that
you can actually
get really good performance
by only allowing up to 1/10
of the parts of the image to
be processed by a sparse layer.
So yeah, we think this is a
really nice direction, too,
in terms of combining
sparsity, along
with adaptive computation.
And yeah, thanks so
much for having us.
That's the talk.
Well, thank you, Barret
and Irwan, for coming here.
So [CLAPS] thanks a lot.
So I will just ask a
bunch of questions.
And then we can have,
after the class,
an open question panel
for the students.
So one thing is, have you tried
using more linear attention
mechanisms, like
reformers and other stuff,
to scale the computation?
I personally haven't.
Maybe--
I haven't,
personally, done this.
Yeah, so I guess we
can maybe comment
on how the cost coming
from the attention maps
isn't the dominant cost in
these large transformers.
So the motivation for
using linear attention,
like performance, is that it
reduces the quadratic cost
of attention.
That's right.
But so far, at least
in some typical NLP
setups like superGLUE, C4, and
so on, as you scale the models,
most of the memory comes
from the model weights,
as opposed to the
attention maps.
That's also because using very
long context or sequence length
doesn't prove that fruitful.
And so just working
with the [INAUDIBLE]
self-attention mechanism is a
very strong baseline already.
Got it.
OK.
So another question is, do
you think this mechanism is
even more scalable?
Can it go on and be like 10
trillion parameter models,
stuff like that?
What do you think?
Yeah, definitely.
I think totally.
I think, honestly, one of the
biggest constraints is that--
and this isn't even
necessarily a constraint--
it's just you have to fit
the parameters somewhere.
And there's just limited
storage on devices.
But if you get enough
devices such that,
yeah, you can just
partition the weights.
It's like yeah, I don't
see anything stopping it.
Got it.
So what do you
think, personally,
is the thing that gives
the direction, like scaling
up transformers will go and do?
Will there be more
works that are
trying to just use this
transformer-like mechanisms,
like mixture of experts?
Or do you think there's
going to be other things
that the community needs?
I mean, definitely think mixture
of experts should find its way,
or at least sparse layers, like
switch transformer and stuff,
will definitely, I
think, find their way
into the future of large models.
I think they really
confer a lot of benefits.
And they're also very good in
high throughput applications.
So I think the one thing--
so the one downside
on sparsity is
if you look at the
performance per model weight,
they're going to always be
worse than dense models.
So it's like if you really
are constrained on I
want to design the
best model I can
to fit on as small
of a device as I can,
then they're probably not
going to be the best solution.
Because the sparse
weights just aren't
as good as just the
dense weight that's
being used for everything.
So I think it really
depends on the application.
But I'm very optimistic
for when we're
training these models during
pretraining with lots of data
parallelism and then we're
serving them in medium
to higher throughput examples,
I feel like they could actually
just be a pretty big win.
So that's kind of
my thoughts on how
I think sparsity will be used.
In terms of other
things, yeah, I think--
I don't know.
There's a ton of
exciting research,
from everything from a lot
of the linear attention
stuff, adaptive computation,
new pretraining objectives.
Yeah, it's hard to know what
the future will look like.
But a lot of exciting
things to look forward to.
Sounds good.
OK.
So we can just now have a
round of student questions.
So I'll just stop the recording.